JOHN ADRIAN TICATIC



+639558225148



john.ticatic@gmail.com



Batangas, Philippines, 4223

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

I am a developer with 2 years of experience creating web applications, desktop applications, and providing hardware troubleshooting and support in corporate settings. I am eager to collaborate with other developers and grow under the guidance of a mentor who can help me showcase my skills while learning from their expertise.

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Batangas State University - Lipa Campus

CERTIFICATIONS & SEMINARS

- Computer System Servicing NCII (TESDA)
- BITS Synergy Conference: "Industry 4.0: A Solution towards Technology Challenges"
- BITS Synergy Conference: "BITS Student

Conference"

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: [JavaScript, Python, C#, VB.NET]
- Web Development: [HTML, CSS, React, Node.js]
- Database Management: [MySQL, MongoDB, Oracle]
- Tools & Platforms: [Git, Visual Studio/Code, Crystal Reports, AI Tools]
- UI / UX : [Adobe Photoshop, Figma]

WORK EXPERIENCE

Computer Programmer

Newborn Screening Center Southern Luzon, January 2024 - Now

The role encompasses creating applications in response to employee requisitions, diagnosing and resolving hardware and software malfunctions within the corporate environment, and undertaking all tasks pertinent to information technology operations.

It Support (Monitoring)

Star Tollway Corporation, Feb 2023 - July 2023

This role encompasses CCTV-based traffic and accident surveillance operations, comprehensive management of the stalled vehicle database—including the addition, modification, and removal of record and the utilization of Microsoft applications and database platforms for detailed data evaluation and analytical reporting.